# Ying-Ying Szeto

yingyingszetoo@gmail.com +1 (646) 421 3288 LinkedIn @yingyingszeto

# **PORTFOLIO**

yingyingszeto.github.io/portfolio

### **EDUCATION**

**User Experience Design** 

Master • Falmouth University Falmouth. UK

Visual and Digital Art

Diploma • Humber College *Toronto, ON, Canada* 

#### **SKILLS**

## Design

UX Strategy User Research

Interaction Design

Wireframing

**Prototyping** 

**Usability Testing** 

Visual Design

#### **Tools**

**Figma** 

Miro

Mural

**Optimal Workshop** 

HTML/CSS/JS

**JIRA** 

## **LANGUAGE**

English Chinese

#### **SUMMARY**

UX / Product Designer with 5 years of experience. I specialize in end-toend product design and have delivered digital solutions for enterprises and startups (B2B and SaaS) in insurance, customer communication, and automotive marketplaces across North America and Asia. I am authorized to work in the US; no sponsorship required.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Senior UX Designer** 

Mar 2021 - Aug 2023 • Hong Kong

**Keyteo Consulting** 

Full-time Onsite at Manulife Financial (John Hancock)

B2B • Insurance

- Designed and delivered solutions that impacted 50k+ insurance agents across Hong Kong, Vietnam, the Philippines, Indonesia, and Malaysia.
- Led end-to-end design for multiple platforms across the sales workflow ecosystem, including mobile and web applications.
- Partnered with research and service design teams to conduct user studies and analysis, informing design decisions and influencing regional user experience strategies.

# **UX/UI Designer**

Jan 2020 - Oct 2020 • Hong Kong

maaiiConnect

B2B SaaS • Customer Support

- Transformed the onboarding experience for SaaS product through a simple and delightful design to guide chatbot installation, reducing customer inquiry tickets by 30% in 2 months.
- Collaborated with product, engineering, and QA teams to ship pixelperfect production matching the design.

# **UX/UI Designer**

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020 • Hong Kong

**EAB Systems** 

B2B SaaS • Insurance

- Created user flows and interface design for client AXA Singapore, a global insurance company, based on a core SaaS product.
- Developed design concepts and pitched them to clients from various insurance enterprises.

# **Web Designer**

Nov 2015 - Apr 2017 • Toronto, ON, Canada

autoTrader.ca

B2C • Automotive marketplace

 Collaborated with the UX team to improve the B2C automotive marketplace interface design.

## Freelance Designer

2013 - Present

• Designed and developed websites for New Era Cap, Glo, Yuki Spa, and small businesses in Canada and Hong Kong.